<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Roborumble</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Roborumble</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboRumble: XR Tele-Steered Humanoid Robots</title>
      <link>/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An immersive experience where participants remotely control humanoid robots in a high-energy, XR-enhanced arena. RoboRumble blends strategy, skill, and engineering in an interactive environment that feels like a live sports event—reimagined with technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Concept Highlights:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Humanoid Robot Design and Customization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participants use modular humanoid robots that can be customized with a range of “abilities” like agility, speed, or defensive features. This lets players craft unique personalities and approaches for their robots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XR-Enhanced Tele-Steering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through VR headsets, controllers, and haptic feedback, participants experience the sensation of being “inside” their robots. This first-person view offers real-time visuals and stats for total situational awareness, making every move feel immersive and engaging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;3&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dynamic Arena with Real-Time Interaction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The XR arena adds layers of strategy, with obstacles, virtual barriers, and safe “challenge zones” that create an evolving environment. Real-world elements, like moving platforms or soft impact zones, blend with digital overlays to add depth without danger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skill-Based Scoring System&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Matches are won by points, rewarding finesse, strategy, and well-timed moves rather than simple takedowns. Points are awarded for achievements like tagging, maneuvering through obstacles, or completing objectives, focusing on skill and creativity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;5&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Community and Spectator Engagement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fans and spectators join the experience through AR/XR, seeing the competition up-close with stats, replays, and even interactive “cheering” features. A global leaderboard and community-driven challenges bring people together for continuous engagement and friendly competition.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
